[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actor received the Razzie Award for Worst Actor for 1982?", "correct_answer": "Laurence Olivier for Inchon", "incorrect_answers": ["Christopher Atkins The Pirate Movie", "Arnold Schwarzenegger for Conan the Barbarian", "Luciano Pavarotti Yes, Giorgio"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This Oscar-winning motion picture, starring Joe Pesci and Robert De Niro, is based on the book Wiseguy by Nicholas Pileggi.", "correct_answer": "Goodfellas", "incorrect_answers": ["Wiseguy: The Movie", "Bad People", "Me and the Mafia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What year did the great 80s flick 48 Hrs.  come out in the movie theatres in the United States?", "correct_answer": "1982", "incorrect_answers": ["1983", "1981", "1984"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When Dr. Craig Venters private company, Celera, declared that they would beat the Human Genome Project in sequencing all human DNA, what did Venter tell Dr. Francis Collins, director of the HGP?", "correct_answer": "You can do mouse.", "incorrect_answers": ["The private sector always wins.", "Just send me all your grant money.", "Why dont you try something easier?"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which movie does Alan Rickman play ranch owner Elliot Marston opposite Tom Selleck?", "correct_answer": "Quigley Down Under", "incorrect_answers": ["Judas Kiss", "Robin Hood: Prince of Thieves", "Love Actually"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of Stella Adlers famous father?", "correct_answer": "Jacob Adler", "incorrect_answers": ["Jay Adler", "Luther Adler", "Charles Adler"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Complete the title of this 1983 song by Prince:\nLittle Red ________", "correct_answer": "Corvette", "incorrect_answers": ["Camaro", "Impala", "Malibu"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Why do flamingos often stand on one leg?", "correct_answer": "Noone knows for sure.", "incorrect_answers": ["To keep their feet from becoming waterlogged.", "To keep feet from getting tired.", "To stir up as little silt from bottom as possible."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Why will worms not live in seaweed fertilizer?", "correct_answer": "Because of its high salt content", "incorrect_answers": ["Because it contains antibiotics that repulse them", "All of these", "Because it is acidic"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who sang the theme song to 1965 James Bond movie, Thunderball?", "correct_answer": "Tom Jones", "incorrect_answers": ["Dean Torrence", "Englebert Humperdinck", "Paul Anka"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Many Royal Navy and US Navy ships are named after this fearful insect. Not just that, but an F/A-18 aircraft and a Honda motorcycle also carry its name.", "correct_answer": "Hornet", "incorrect_answers": ["Tarantula", "Cicada", "Yellowjacket"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Udo Kier, who played Vampire Elder Dragonetti in Blade, also starred in what 1974 horror movie?", "correct_answer": "Blood For Dracula", "incorrect_answers": ["The Texas Chainsaw Massacre", "Abby", "Black Christmas"]}]